etech.com 2012-11-01

# Privacy Policy : eTech.com

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at eTech.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

**Information Collection**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.   

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses eTech.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of eTech.com on other Web sites. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

**Information Use**  
eTech.com does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We use the information we collect to:  
provide you with information and services you request   
customize your experience on the eTech.com  
communicate with you about your orders, service updates and other administrative issues   
measure and improve our sites and services   
resolve disputes, address complaints and troubleshoot technical problems   
analyze site and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports 

**About Cookies**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features, personalized advertisements on other Web sites, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.   
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of eTech.com's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any eTech.com products and services that require you to Sign in. 

**Security**  
We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization. We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Links**  
eTech.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**General**  
we will change and update the Privacy Policy from time to time without any prior notice. Please be aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose in Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about the Privacy Notice, please contact us at: service@etech.com.
